- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- Welcome to Captain Galactic's Pizzatarium, where--
欢迎来到银河队长披萨馆，这里——
- Where the pizza is out of this world.
这里的披萨超乎想象。
[laughs] All right, here we go.
[笑声] 好了，我们开始吧。
Okay, we are gonna take two galactic sized
好的，我们要两份银河大小的
meat-eor lovers pizzas, right?
肉食爱好者披萨，对吧？
- Sorry, we're just a little excited.
抱歉，我们只是有点兴奋。
We're celebrating a special birthday boy today.
我们今天在庆祝一个特别的生日男孩。
- Oh, really?
哦，真的吗？
Which little space cadet's birthday is it?
哪个小太空学员的生日呢？
- Mine! Tommy Harper,
我的！汤米·哈珀，
reporting for space duty.
报到执行太空任务。
- Dad, don't embarrass us. - What?
爸爸，别让我们尴尬。 - 什么？
- We're too old for this place.
我们太老了，不适合这里。
- Please get out of the rocket booster seat.
请从火箭助推器座位上下来。
- [groans] Fine.
好吧。
- Oh! - Dad! - Watch it. - Whoa!
哦！ - 爸爸！ - 小心。 - 哇！
- Be careful. Be careful.
小心点。小心点。
Oh! - I got it.
哦！ - 我弄好了。
- Geez.
天哪。
- Dicky's lucky he's in Australia
迪基在澳大利亚真幸运，
and doesn't have to see this.
不用看到这一幕。
- Come on, kids. You used to love
来吧，孩子们。你们以前
having your birthday parties here.
很喜欢在这里开生日派对的。
- Sorry, Mom. Mae and I are just
对不起，妈妈。梅和我只是
really stressed out about our French Club trip.
对我们的法语俱乐部旅行感到非常紧张。
- If we don't find jobs soon, we won't be able to pay
如果我们不尽快找到工作，我们就无法支付
the mandatory student-earned portion of the travel fee.
旅行费用中必须由学生赚取的部分。
- And then we'll never get to Paris.
那样我们就永远去不了巴黎了。
- Paris, Paris, Paris.
巴黎，巴黎，巴黎。
- All you ever talk about is Paris.
你总是说巴黎。
- Come on, Nicky. Let's go to the arcade
来吧，Nicky。我们去游戏厅，
where no one is talking about Paris.
那里没人谈论巴黎。
Okay, let's talk about Paris.
好吧，我们来谈谈巴黎。
We need to make sure Dawn has enough money to go to Paris
我们需要确保Dawn有足够的钱去巴黎，
so we can turn her room into our man cave
这样我们就可以把她的房间变成我们的男人窝
for seven whole days.
整整七天。
- Better make it six. We're gonna need a full day
最好改成六天。我们需要一整天
to air it out.
来通风。
- Fair enough. But that's not gonna happen
- 说得有理。但那是不可能的
if she can't afford to go.
如果她负担不起的话。
That's why we're gonna win that hoverboard
所以我们打算赢得那个悬浮滑板
and sell it to help her make money for her trip.
然后卖掉它来帮她筹集旅费。
- I don't know.
- 我不确定。
We're terrible at these games.
我们玩这些游戏很糟糕。
Last time we played, we accidentally
上次我们玩的时候，不小心
hit Dicky in the head with a skee ball.
用滚球打中了迪基的头。
- Relax. We're much better now.
- 放松点。我们现在好多了。
- How did we hit ourselves in the head with skee balls?
- 我们是怎么用滚球打到自己头的？
- Ah, excuse me, I ordered the, uh,
- 啊，对不起，我点了那个，呃，
super solar system big boy birthday sundae
超级太阳系大男孩生日圣代
a light-year ago--what?
一个光年前——什么？
- Maybe you girls could get jobs here.
- 也许你们女孩可以在这里找工作。
- Clearly they need the help!
- 显然他们需要帮助！
- Well, it's a good idea. You both have restaurant experience.
- 嗯，这是个好主意。你们俩都有餐厅经验。
- They hire young people.
- 他们雇佣年轻人。
[clattering]
[叮叮当当]
- See? Look how young that bus boy is.
- 看？看看那个餐车男孩多年轻。
- Sorry for the mess.
- 抱歉弄得一团糟。
- That's not a bad idea.
那主意不错。
That waitress just got a $20 tip.
那个女服务员刚得到了20美元的小费。
- It's actually a great idea. A few weeks working here,
实际上这是个绝妙的主意。在这里工作几周，
and we'll make our Paris money in no time.
我们很快就能赚够去巴黎的钱。
We need to apply today.
我们今天就得申请。
- This is ridiculous. Where is my sundae?
这太荒谬了。我的圣代在哪里？
I'm gonna complain to the manager.
我要向经理投诉。
all: No.
不行。
- Why not? It is my birthday!
为什么不行？今天可是我的生日！
- We're gonna apply for jobs here,
我们要在这里申请工作，
and we don't want you ruining our chances.
我们不想你毁了我们的机会。
- Plus, if you complain,
而且，如果你投诉的话，
it'll be extremely embarrassing.
那会非常尴尬的。
- Fine, I won't complain.
好吧，我不投诉了。
But I am sitting on my rocket booster seat.
但我要坐在我的火箭助推座椅上。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪  ♪
♪  ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
♪ 欢快的音乐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ 吹口哨 ♪
- I don't know. Je ne sais pas.
- 我不知道。♪ 我不知道 ♪
No, Squish. I didn't say "paw."
不，Squish。我没说“爪子”。
I said "pas" .
我说的是 ♪ 不是 ♪。
You're too cute.
你太可爱了。
High pas.
高高的 ♪ 不是 ♪。
- Dawn!
- Dawn！
Captain Galactic's Pizzatarium called me
Captain Galactic的披萨店给我打电话了
and said I got the job. Paris, here we come.
并说我已经得到了这份工作。巴黎，我们来了。
Yes! Or should I say, "Oui oui"?
是的！或者我应该说，“Oui oui”？
- Well, I didn't get a call.
- 嗯，我没有接到电话。
So it may just be "you you."
所以可能只是“你你”。
- Well, I'm sure you'll get the call soon.
- 嗯，我相信你很快就会接到电话的。
- You're right. I just need to be patient.
- 你说得对。我只需要耐心等待。
- Yeah. - I can be patient.
- 是的。- 我可以耐心等待。
- Yeah. - I'm a patient person.
- 是的。- 我是一个有耐心的人。
- Exactly. - Patient, patient, patient.
- 没错。- 耐心，耐心，耐心。
[laughs] Ring!
[笑] 铃响了！
I need you to ring. I've been practicing all day.
我需要你来敲铃。我一整天都在练习。
Please, I'm begging you.
求你了，我在求你。
[speaking French]
[说法语]
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
Maybe we should practice our French
也许我们应该练习我们的法语
to get your mind off things.
来让你暂时忘掉这些事。
- Yeah, good idea. - Okay.
- 对，好主意。 - 好的。
Je travaille dans un café.
Which means, "I work at a café."
这意味着，“我在咖啡馆工作。”
[snorts and laughs] That's funny.
[哼笑并笑出声] 这很有趣。
I work at a café.
我在一家咖啡馆工作。
Okay, let's try something else.
好吧，让我们试试别的。
J'ai un bon travail et mon amie ne l'a pas.
我有一份好工作，而我的朋友没有。
Which means, "I have a good job and my friend doesn't."
这意味着，“我有一份好工作，而我的朋友没有。”
- Why would that even be in the book?
为什么这会出现在书里？
- Je ne sais pas.
我不知道。
- So how much do you think all this stuff is worth?
那你觉得这些东西值多少钱？
100? - 200?
100？- 200？
[snap] - Four bucks.
[啪] - 四块钱。
- For all this? - No, for my time.
所有这些？- 不，是给我的时间。
This stuff is worthless.
这些东西一文不值。
- Worthless? Okay, now how are we
- 一文不值？好吧，那我们怎么
gonna get Dawn to Paris?
让Dawn去巴黎呢？
- This is a big problem.
- 这是个大问题。
- You think you guys got problems?
- 你们觉得有麻烦？
I can't get out of these things.
我连这些东西都脱不掉。
- Just push in. - Well, I did,
- 用力推进去。
but then I got nervous, and the stress
- 我试过了，
made my fingers swell.
但后来我紧张了，压力让我的手指肿了。
- Why did you put them on all of your fingers?
- 你为什么把它们戴在所有手指上？
- I put them on when I thought I could get out.
- 我戴上它们的时候，以为我能脱下来。
It was a joke. It was supposed to be funny.
这是个玩笑。本意是想逗乐的。
- And it is. [boys laughing]
- 确实挺逗的。[男孩们笑]
- Okay, how are we gonna get Dawn to Paris?
- 好吧，我们怎么把Dawn送到巴黎去？
- You should've let your dad complain
- 你本该让你爸在银河队长的披萨店抱怨的。
at Captain Galactic's Pizzaterium.
- [嗤之以鼻] 还要让我们难堪？不了，谢谢。
- [scoffs] And embarrass us? No, thank you.
- 男孩们，男孩们。总是抱怨。
- Boys, boys. Always complain.
我父母经常在那里抱怨。
My parents complain there all the time.
经理总是给我们免费食物和代币。
And the manager always gives us free food and tokens.
- 那是个好主意。我觉得Dooley有点门道。
- That's a great idea.
那是个好主意。
I think Dooley's on to something.
我觉得多利找到了点子。
Maybe we should do that.
也许我们应该这么做。
- Yeah. With enough free tokens,
是的。有了足够的免费代币，
we'll be able to win the hoverboard
我们就能赢得悬浮滑板
and get Dawn to Paris.
并让唐去巴黎。
- But what if there's nothing to complain about?
但如果没什么可抱怨的呢？
- Then you make it up. They can't prove
那就编造一些。他们无法证明
you didn't just eat a mouthful of fleas.
你刚才没有吃了一嘴跳蚤。
- It's an odd example, but I'm still on board.
这是个奇怪的例子，但我还是同意。
- Yeah. - Seriously, guys. A little help?
- 是的。 - 说真的，伙计们。帮帮忙？
- Okay, well, don't fight it.
- 好吧，别抗拒。
The swelling will go down if you just relax.
放松点，肿胀会消退的。
- Well, that's easy for you to say.
- 对你来说当然容易说。
You know, what if I have to go pee?
你知道，如果我得去小便怎么办？
Great, now I have to go pee.
糟糕，我现在得去小便了。
[yells] Oh, oh, oh!
[大喊] 哦，哦，哦！
Guys, I think I dislocated my arms.
伙计们，我觉得我的手臂脱臼了。
- Do you need us to pop them back in for you?
- 需要我们帮你复位吗？
- Oh, no time!
- 哦，没时间了！
Oh, it's a button fly!
哦，这是按扣式裤链！
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
- That's my phone. Whoa, whoa.
- 那是我的电话。哇，哇。
Where's my phone? [ringing continues]
我的电话在哪里？[铃声继续]
It's in my hand and it's still ringing!
在我手里，还在响！
Why aren't I answering it?
我为什么不接电话？
- Just answer it. - Answer it?
- 接电话吧。 - 接电话？
- Answer it!
- 接电话！
- Hello?
- 喂？
Yeah. Yes, yeah, I--
是的。是的，是的，我--
Yes, I understand. Thank you.
是的，我明白了。谢谢。
I got the job! - Yes!
我得到那份工作了！ - 太好了！
- Mon gateau a reçu un travail
我的蛋糕得到了一份工作
et mon amie est un pamplemousse.
而我的朋友是一个葡萄柚。
Which means, "I got a good job and my friend did, too."
这意味着，“我得到了一份好工作，我的朋友也得到了。”
- Actually, you said, "My cake got a job,
- 实际上，你说的意思是，“我的蛋糕得到了一份工作，
and my friend is a grapefruit."
而我的朋友是一个葡萄柚。”
- Okay, in Paris, you do the talking.
- 好吧，在巴黎，你来负责说话。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Are you sure we can handle all these wild kids?
你确定我们能应付这些野孩子吗？
- Yeah, it's no different than my house.
- 当然，跟我家里没什么两样。
[splat]
[啪]
There's even flying pizza.
甚至还有飞来飞去的披萨。
- I'll be right with you two.
- 我马上就来找你们。
Hey, would you take this to table seven, please?
嘿，你能把这个送到七号桌吗？
Thank you.
谢谢。
So, how can I help you guys?
那么，我能帮你们什么忙呢？
both: Wally?
两人：沃利？
- Uh, that's Assistant Space Commander Wally to you.
- 呃，我是太空副指挥官沃利，对你来说。
These stripes don't just happen, ladies.
这些条纹可不是无缘无故出现的，女士们。
- Didn't you used to work at Urbina Outfitters in the mall?
- 你以前不是在购物中心里的Urbina Outfitters工作吗？
- Oh, yeah, for a hot second.
- 哦，对，就一小段时间。
Till Justin started working there
直到Justin开始在那里工作
and got all assistant bossy on me.
然后对我指手画脚的。
Well, who's the assistant boss now?
那现在谁是助理老板呢？
Moi.
我。
- What?
- 什么？
- It's French for "me."
- 这是法语，意思是“我”。
- Oh, oh. Yeah, yeah. [chuckles]
- 哦，哦。是的，是的。[轻笑]
So, we're your new space-tresses.
那么，我们现在是你的新太空女主人了。
This is gonna be so much fun working for you.
为你工作一定会很有趣。
- Yeah. - Oh, no, it's not.
- 是的。 - 哦，不，不会的。
You see, Assistant Space Commander Wally
你知道，助理太空指挥官沃利
runs a very tight ship. Now, about your costumes.
管理得非常严格。现在，关于你们的服装。
- Ooh, I was thinking I could be a galactic princess.
- 哦，我在想我可以扮演一个银河公主。
- And I could be, like, a space warrior.
- 而我可以扮演一个太空战士。
- That would be amazing,
- 那会非常棒，
if you got to choose your outfits.
如果你们能选择自己的服装。
Which you don't. You have to race for them.
但你们不能。你们必须通过比赛来获得它们。
- Race? [both laughing]
- 比赛？[两人笑]
- I'm serious.
- 我是认真的。
Go. Oh, by the way,
去吧。哦，顺便说一下，
only one of them's been cleaned.
只有一件是干净的。
- This isn't so bad, right?
- 这还不算太糟，对吧？
- Do you have any idea how bad this helmet smells?
- 你知道这头盔有多臭吗？
[sniffs and gags]
[嗅了嗅并作呕]
[in electronic voice] Nope, can't do it.
[用电子声音说]不行，我做不到。
- Sorry, Bleep-Blop, but the helmet stays on
- 抱歉，Bleep-Blop，但头盔必须一直戴着，好吗？
at all times, all right?
无论如何，头盔不能摘。
You guys are doing great, though.
你们做得很好。
- Cheer up, Bleep-Blop.
振作点，Bleep-Blop。
Remember, we're doing this for Paris.
记住，我们这么做是为了巴黎。
- [in electronic voice] Bleep-Blop sad.
[电子声音] Bleep-Blop 很难过。
[electronic beeping]
[电子哔哔声]
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
Greetings. I am your service droid.
大家好，我是您的服务机器人。
My name is...
我的名字是...
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨。
It's me. Mae.
是我，Mae。
- Nice to meet you, Memay.
- 很高兴见到你，Memay。
- No, it's me. Mae.
- 不，是我。Mae。
- Yeah, we heard you. Your name is Memay.
- 是的，我们听到了。你的名字是Memay。
- No, it's me. Mae.
- 不，是我。Mae。
- Jeez, we got a pushy robot.
- 天啊，我们遇到了一个固执的机器人。
- Helmet. [clang]
- 头盔。[铛]
- You know what? Just give me your order.
- 你知道吗？直接告诉我你的订单。
- We will have a galaxy-sized meteor pizza
- 我们要一个银河大小的陨石披萨
and two onion rings of Saturn.
和两份土星洋葱圈。
- Fine. I'll have that back to you
- 好的。我会尽快给你准备好
at warp speed.
以超光速送达。
- Okay, time to put Dooley's plan into motion.
好的，是时候实施杜利的计划了。
The more we complain, the more tokens we'll get.
我们抱怨得越多，得到的代币就越多。
Houston, we've got a problem here.
休斯顿，我们这里有问题。
- [groans] Never heard that one before.
（呻吟）从来没听过这个。
[sighs] Everything all right
（叹气）这里一切都好吗，太空学员们？
over here, space cadets?
别叫我们‘太空学员’。
- Don't "space cadet" us.
我们没心情被称作‘太空学员’。
- We are in no mood to be space cadetted.
这食物简直是太空垃圾。
This food is space junk.
你的食物还没进入你的餐桌范围呢。
- Your food hasn't even entered your table sphere yet.
- 你们的餐点还没进入你们的餐桌领域呢。
- And that's another thing. Where is our food?
- 还有，我们的食物呢？
- The service in this dump is terrible.
- 这地方的服务糟透了。
- Yeah, I just ate a mouthful of fleas.
- 是啊，我刚吃了一嘴跳蚤。
You can't prove I didn't.
你无法证明我没有。
- I have to say, we're regulars.
- 我得说，我们是常客。
But after this terrible experience,
但经过这次糟糕的经历，
I'm not sure if we can ever come back.
我不确定我们还能不能再来。
- My deepest Apollo-gies. - Oh.
- 我深表歉意。 - 哦。
- To make it up to you,
- 为了补偿你们，
here are some free alien mustaches.
这里有几个免费的异形小胡子。
- Sold. - No.
- 成交。 - 不。
- Fine. We'll take all the free tokens
- 好吧。我们把所有能拿的免费代币都拿走。
we can carry. - No, I have something
- 不，我有更好的东西，
much better, something that'll leave you
更好的东西，会让你们更加满意。
far more satisfied.
- 他要给我们悬浮滑板。
- He's gonna give us the hoverboard.
- 呃，嘿，Bleep-Blop。亲爱的？
- Um, hey, Bleep-Blop. Sweetie?
过来一下，好吗？
Come over here a sec, okay?
嘿，呃...
Hey, um...
你被解雇了。
you're fired.
both: What?
- I'm what?
- You're fired? [laughs]
There. Now this tin can won't have to ruin
anyone's meals ever again.
All right? Okay.
- I can't believe we just got Memay fired.
- You didn't get Memay fired.
You got me, Mae, fired!
- Who got you fired?
- 谁让你被解雇了？
- Uh, they just left. - Let's go get 'em.
- 呃，他们刚走。 - 我们去追他们。
Forgot my 'staches.
忘了我的小胡子。
- Now Memay mad.
- 现在Memay生气了。
- Pretty pretty space princess mad too.
- 漂亮的太空公主也很生气。
- ♪ Oh-oh-oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
哦-哦-哦，哦，哦
- [whistling]
[吹口哨]
- Do you think the girls will realize
- 你觉得女孩们会意识到
it was just an honest mistake, and forgive us?
这只是个无心的错误，并原谅我们吗？
- Wouldn't bet on it.
- 我可不这么认为。
- Why not?
为什么不？
Ah! - I can't believe
啊！
you guys got Mae fired for what I assume
我简直不敢相信
is some stupid, selfish reason.
你们因为我觉得是一些愚蠢自私的原因让Mae被解雇了。
- You don't know that it was some stupid, selfish reason.
你不知道那是因为一些愚蠢自私的原因。
Okay, it totally was.
好吧，确实是。
- Not only did you cost Mae her chance at going to Paris,
你不仅让Mae失去了去巴黎的机会，
but you cost me my chance at going too.
还让我也失去了去的机会。
- Wait, why can't you go?
等等，你为什么不能去？
- Well, after testing me on my French,
嗯，在我测试了我的法语之后，
Mom and Dad said I can only go if Mae goes.
妈妈和爸爸说只有梅去我才能去。
She's the only one of us who can parlez Français.
我们中只有她能说法语。
Whatever that means.
不管那是什么意思。
- Look, we're really sorry.
- 听着，我们真的很抱歉。
But don't worry. We can get Mae her job back.
但别担心，我们可以帮梅找回工作。
We'll fix this.
我们会解决这个问题的。
- No. No fixing this.
- 不，无法解决。
You're not doing anything except staying as far away
你们什么都别做，除了离银河队长比萨店越远越好。
from Captain Galactic's Pizzatarium as possible.
看来我们只能忘记巴黎了。
- Well, it looks like we're just gonna have to forget about Paris.
- 不，我们不能。我们一直梦想着去巴黎。
- No, we can't. We've been dreaming
不，我们不能。我们一直梦想
about going to Paris.
去巴黎。
- Looks like we're just gonna have to forget
看来我们只能忘记
about our man cave.
我们的男人洞穴。
- No, we can't. We've been dreaming
不，我们不能。我们一直梦想
about our man cave.
我们的男人洞穴。
- How about this? Starting tomorrow,
这样如何？从明天开始，
I'll work double shifts. That way,
我将上双班。这样，
I can earn enough money for the both of us to go.
我可以赚足够的钱让我们俩去。
- How about this? Tomorrow after Dawn's shift,
这样如何？明天在Dawn的班次之后，
we'll get their manager to hire Mae back.
我们会说服他们的经理重新雇佣Mae。
That way, they get to go, and we get our man cave.
这样，他们可以去，我们也能得到我们的男人窝。
- Can we come to your man cave?
- 我们能去你的男人窝吗？
- Not if you're gonna do that.
- 如果你要那样做的话，不行。
- Fine. Then we won't come
- 好吧。那我们就不去了。
to your man cave.
去你的男人窝。
Fry me.
炸了我吧。
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [咕哝声]
Okay. [grunting]
好的。[咕哝声]
Hi, be right with you.
嗨，马上就来。
Watch the crown!
小心皇冠！
No. Ah!
不。啊！
[sighs] Made it.
[叹气] 终于到了。
- Sorry about the kids.
- 抱歉孩子们闹腾。
- No, it's all good. Just a little space fight.
- 没事，都挺好的。只是小打小闹。
- Here. - Yeah.
- 给你。 - 嗯。
And the hot pizza they threw at me earlier.
还有之前他们朝我扔的热披萨。
Thanks.
谢谢。
And the spaghetti they put in my shoe.
还有他们塞在我鞋子里的意大利面。
- Oh, gosh. - [chuckles]
哦，天哪。
Thank you so much. It's a pleasure serving you.
非常感谢。为您服务是我的荣幸。
Be sure to ask for me every time you come back.
每次回来记得找我。
- Thanks.
谢谢。
- All right, space princess. You can blast off.
好了，太空公主。你可以起飞了。
Your shift's over.
你的班次结束了。
- Oh, I was actually wondering if you'd let me work
哦，我其实想问你能不能让我今天加班。请？
a double shift today. Please?
真的吗？你还想要更多这样的工作？
- Seriously? You want more of this?
当然想。这不就是我们在这里工作的原因吗？
[clanging and shattering]
[叮当声和破碎声]
- Of course I do. Isn't that why we work here?
- 当然想。这不是我们在这里工作的原因吗？
'Cause we love the kids?
- 因为我们爱孩子们？
[door whirs]
[门嗡嗡作响]
- I say, I say, I say.
- 我说，我说，我说。
You, sir. Are you the manager
- 先生，您是这里的经理吗？
of this here establishment?
- 谁想知道？
- Who wants to know?
- 雷金纳德·法伯·朱尼尔三世。
- Reginald Farber Junior the Third.
- 律师。
Attorney at law.
[笑声] 你不能当真。
- [laughs] You cannot be serious.
- [笑] 你不是认真的吧。
- As serious as a three-legged possum in a slanted outhouse.
- 认真得就像一个三条腿的负鼠在一个倾斜的户外厕所里。
Now, my client, Mae B. Valentine,
现在，我的当事人，梅·B·瓦伦丁，
was fired unjustly, unkindly,
被不公正、不友好地，
and in a most un-southernly manner.
以及极其不合南方风格的方式解雇了。
I insist you reinstate her immediately
我坚持要求你立即恢复她的职位
or face a lawsuit for wrongful termination.
否则将面临不当解雇的诉讼。
- How old are you? - Older than a three-legged
- 你多大了？ - 比一个三条腿的
possum in a slanted outhouse.
负鼠在倾斜的户外厕所里还要老。
- Right, um, please leave before I blast you
- 好吧，嗯，请在我用太空炮轰你之前离开。
out of a space cannon. - I'm insult--oh!
从太空大炮里。- 我被侮辱了——哦！
All right, time for plan B.
好吧，是时候执行B计划了。
Hey, Miles. Get in here.
嘿，迈尔斯。进来。
[door whirring]
[门嗡嗡作响]
Excuse me, sir.
对不起，先生。
- Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
- 哦，你一定是在开玩笑。
- Now, this poor young man
- 现在，这个可怜的年轻人
sustained a grave injury at your Live Long and Pasta bar.
在你的“活久见和意面”酒吧遭受了严重的伤害。
Now, I may be a simple country lawyer,
现在，我可能只是一个简单的乡村律师，
but this looks like a clear case of fettucine al-falldo.
但这看起来像是明显的“意大利宽面摔倒案”。
- You did not just say that.
- 你不会是这么说的吧。
- I surely did.
- 我确实说了。
If you don't give Mae B. Valentine her job back,
如果你不把梅·B·瓦伦丁的工作还给她，
you will be hearing from my attorney.
你会收到我的律师的信。
- I thought you were an attorney.
- 我以为你就是律师。
- Then you will be hearing from me.
- 那你会收到我的信。
Argument won. Case closed.
争论结束。案件关闭。
When does she start?
她什么时候开始？
- The only thing I'll be hearing from you is this.
- 我只会从你那里听到这个。
- Ow!
- 哎哟！
- And the same goes for your friend here
- 你的这位朋友也一样
with the fake injury.
假装受伤的那位。
- Ow!
- 哎哟！
- Ah, okay.
- 啊，好吧。
Hey, Ricky? Time for Plan C.
嘿，Ricky？该执行C计划了。
[door whirring]
[门发出嗡嗡声]
- I'm the health inspector, and this place
- 我是卫生检查员，这个地方
has a clear violation of--
明显违反了——
Oh!
哦！
- Ricky? What are you doing here?
- Ricky？你在这里做什么？
- Wait, you know him? - Yeah, he's my brother.
- 等等，你认识他？ - 是的，他是我哥哥。
- And I'm assuming you know the southern dumbbell too?
- 那我猜你也认识那个南方的傻瓜吧？
- Unhand me, you wretched scoundrel!
- 放开我，你这个可恶的恶棍！
- [groans] Another brother.
- [呻吟] 又是一个哥哥。
- Oh, good. The whole family's out of here.
- 哦，太好了。全家人都离开这里了。
- Yes, go. - I said the whole family.
- 是的，走吧。 - 我说的是全家人。
That means you, too, princess.
- 那也包括你，公主。
- What? - Yeah, you're fired.
- 什么？ - 是的，你被解雇了。
- Wha-- But this wasn't even my fault.
- 什...但这根本不是我的错。
- If you need representation,
- 如果你需要代表，
I specialize in wrongful terminations.
我专门处理不当解雇案件。
- Yeah, causing them.
- 是的，制造这些案件。
- Now, now, now. I'll do it myself.
- 现在，现在，现在。我自己来处理。
Ow!
哎哟！
- Guess this means we won't be needing plan D.
- 看来我们不需要D计划了。
You can come out, Squish. We don't need you.
你可以出来了，Squish。我们不需要你了。
♪
- I hope some of the kids who are going to Paris can use these.
- 我希望去巴黎的孩子们能用得上这些。
- Because Paris for us is just une rue à sens unique  avec une sauce bibliothèque.
- 因为对我们来说，巴黎就是一条单行道，配上图书馆酱。
- A one-way street with library sauce?
- 一条单行道配上图书馆酱？
- Yes, Mae. It's a common expression used in France.
是的，梅。这是法国常用的一个表达。
But we're never going to hear it
但我们永远不会听到它
because we're not going to Paris.
因为我们不去巴黎。
[accordion music]
[手风琴音乐]
- What's that music?
那是什么音乐？
♪ ♪
- Uh, what's going on?
呃，发生什么事了？
- [imitating French accent] Welcome to "Café Pari."
[模仿法国口音] 欢迎来到“巴黎咖啡馆”。
- That's French for "Café Paris."
那是法语的“巴黎咖啡馆”。
- I hope you mademoiselles like authentic crepes.
希望各位女士喜欢正宗的可丽饼。
Ah-huh-huh-huh!
啊-哈哈-哈哈！
- Are you okay? - Yes.
- 你还好吗？ - 是的。
Just laughing like a French person.
只是在像法国人一样笑。
Ah-huh-huh-huh! - That's not how they laugh.
啊-哈哈-哈哈！ - 他们不是这样笑的。
They laugh like this. Eh-heh-heh-heh!
他们笑起来是这样的。欸-嘿-嘿-嘿！
- Ah-huh-huh-huh! - Eh-heh-heh-heh!
- 啊-哈哈-哈哈！ - 欸-嘿-嘿-嘿！
- Huh-huh-huh. - Heh-heh-heh.
- 哈-哈-哈。 - 嘿-嘿-嘿。
- Huh-huh-huh! - Heh-heh-heh!
- 哈-哈-哈！ - 嘿-嘿-嘿！
- Guys!
- 伙计们！
Stop!
停！
- Sorry. Look.
对不起。看。
We know we messed up both of your chances to go to Paris.
我们知道我们搞砸了你们俩去巴黎的机会。
- So we thought we'd bring a little bit of Paris to you.
所以我们想把一点巴黎带到你们面前。
♪ ♪
- Wow, this is sweet.
哇，这真贴心。
- So you accept our apology?
那你们接受我们的道歉吗？
- Oh, no, I was talking about this crepe.
哦，不，我说的是这个可丽饼。
It's delicious. [laughs]
它很好吃。[笑]
But, yeah, yeah. Apology accepted.
不过，是的，是的。道歉接受了。
- Mmm. Me, too.
嗯。我也是。
Too bad there's no restaurant in town that serves these.
真可惜镇上没有餐厅供应这些。
You guys could make a fortune.
你们可以赚大钱。
♪ ♪
- Nicky, how many of these crepes can you make?
- Nicky，你能做多少个这种可丽饼？
- As many as you want. Why?
- 你想多少个就多少个。怎么了？
- I think I just found a way to get to Paris
- 我想我找到了一个去巴黎的方法
by bringing Paris to Boulder. Huh-huh-huh!
通过把巴黎带到博尔德。呵呵呵！
- Heh. Eh, I told you.
- 嘿。呃，我告诉过你。
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
- Play, play.
开始，开始。
[accordion music playing]
[手风琴音乐响起]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Frère Jacques ♪
♪雅克兄弟♪
♪ Frère Jacques ♪
♪ Dormez-vous, dormez-vous ♪
♪睡了吗，睡了吗♪
♪ Sonnez les matines, sonnez les matines ♪
♪敲响晨祷钟，敲响晨祷钟♪
♪ Ding ding dong, ding ding dong ♪
♪叮叮当，叮叮当♪
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Merci, merci. [giggles]
谢谢，谢谢。[咯咯笑]
Oh, and don't forget that all of the profits
from the Get Francey Café are going toward
Dawn and Mae's trip to Paris.
Merci.
- Two mushroom and brie crepes. - Bon appétit.
- C'est parfait.
- Okay.
Parfait!
- Baby steps. - Gracias.
- No.
- And remember, madames and messieurs,
记住，女士们先生们，
at Get Sporty, you will always find
在Get Sporty，您总能找到
all of your sporting good needs.
所有您需要的体育用品。
[accordion music plays]
[手风琴音乐播放]
♪ Who loves soccer, Who loves soccer ♪
♪ 谁爱足球，谁爱足球 ♪
♪ How 'bout you? How 'bout you? ♪
♪ 你呢？你呢？ ♪
♪ Everybody eats here ♪
♪ 这里人人都能用餐 ♪
♪ You can buy some cleats here ♪
♪ 你可以在这里买些钉鞋 ♪
♪ And balls too, and balls too ♪
♪ 还有球，还有球 ♪
Hey, I almost pulled a hammy, huh?
嘿，我差点拉伤腿筋，是吧？
Hey, all right. Merci. [cheers and applause]
嘿，好吧。谢谢。[欢呼和掌声]
- Thanks, guys. The Get Francey Café is a hit.
- 谢谢，伙计们。Get Francey咖啡馆很受欢迎。
- [imitating French accent] Our pleasure.
- [模仿法国口音] 我们的荣幸。
- Even Wally loves this place.
- 连Wally也喜欢这个地方。
- Yeah, and if the café stays this popular,
- 是啊，如果咖啡馆一直这么受欢迎，
we should make our money for Paris by the end of the day.
我们今天结束前应该能赚够去巴黎的钱。
- Another order of crepes, monsieur?
- 再来一份可丽饼，先生？
- Oh, yes, please. I must say,
- 哦，好的，请。我得说，
you guys are doing a really good job
你们处理这群人做得真不错。
handling this crowd.
也许我解雇你们两个是个错误。
Maybe I made a mistake firing you two.
both: And?
两个声音：然后呢？
- And get me my crepes.
- 然后给我拿我的可丽饼来。
- Excuse me, I think these crepes
- 对不起，我觉得这些可丽饼
are making my son sick.
让我儿子不舒服。
We'd like a refund.
我们想要退款。
- I don't feel so good.
- 我感觉不太好。
- My crepes aren't making you sick.
- 我的可丽饼不会让你生病的。
Pfft, I know what you're up to.
噗，我知道你在打什么主意。
J'accuse!
我指控！
- Fake complaining so you can get
- 装病想白吃一顿。
a meal on the house.
- 在这里可没门，先生。
Well, that doesn't work here, monsieur.
- 哼哼哼！- 嘿嘿嘿！
- Ah-huh-huh-huh! - Heh-heh-heh!
- 哼哼哼！- 嘿嘿嘿嘿！
- Ah-huh-huh-huh! - Heh-heh-heh-heh!
- 哼。
- Ah-huh.
- 但是煎饼有问题。
- But there's something wrong with them.
- 我们会判断的。
- We'll be the judge of that.
是的。
Yes.
这尝起来没问题。- 太妙了。
This tastes fine. - It's magnifique.
- 哼哼哼。- 嘿嘿嘿。
- Huh-huh-huh. - Heh-heh-heh.
- Huh-huh-huh! - Heh-heh-heh!
[both groaning]
- That's bad. - Very bad.
- [scoffs]
I told you brie wasn't something
you get at a gas station. - [groaning]
- Uh, how many people had the brie?
Uh-oh.
- Oh, no. We have to make this right.
- ♪ Here's your refund, here's your refund ♪
♪ 这是您的退款，这是您的退款 ♪
♪ Please don't sue, please don't sue ♪
♪ 请不要起诉，请不要起诉 ♪
- ♪ Our bathroom's out of order ♪
♪ 我们的洗手间坏了 ♪
♪ But there's one at the drug store ♪
♪ 但药店有一个 ♪
♪ Just buy gum, just buy gum ♪
♪ 买些口香糖吧，买些口香糖 ♪
- If we have to give everyone refunds,
如果我们必须给每个人退款，
how are we gonna pay for Paris?
我们怎么支付去巴黎的费用？
- Uh, so, Wally.
呃，那么，沃利。
Uh, can we have our old jobs back?
呃，我们能恢复原来的工作吗？
- Uh, yeah, if you give me some money for gum.
呃，可以，如果你给我一些买口香糖的钱。
- Yeah.
是的。
- I'm gonna need a lot more gum.
我需要更多的口香糖。
[groans]
（呻吟声）
[whispers] Thank you.
（低语）谢谢。
- We're going to Paris!
我们要去巴黎了！
- Yeah! - High five!
是的！ - 击掌！
[barks] Oh, sorry, Squishy.
（吠叫）哦，对不起，Squishy。
High paw.
击掌。
- ♪ Oh-oh, oh, oh ♪ [barking]
（唱）哦-哦，哦，哦
♪ Oh-oh, oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
（唱）哦-哦，哦，哦-哦-哦
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪